yuvastyle.com 2014-02-28

# Privacy Policy

Yuvastyle.com is an e-Commerce Company owned by Yuvastyle Retail Pvt Ltd offering lifestyle and fashion products for youth in India, based at Land of Entrepreneurs Ahmedabad, Gujarat.

We truly respect your privacy and it is extremely important for us to maintain confidentiality of your personal information shared with us.

**The below privacy policy only applies to our site:**

(A)  We collect your personal information only for below purposes which are for your utmost benefit:

  * Help you to experience an extremely user friendly website
  * Registering on our Website which would require you to fill in your personal details
  * Creating content that will be beneficial to you.
  * Update you regarding our new offerings and events.
  * Notify your Order details and all the further communication related with the same.

(b)  We do not take any liability for any unauthorized access and disclosure of your personal information by third party/person who are not subject to our control. These parties may include advertisers and third party websites that might be linked to Yuvastyle.com.

(c )  During your visit to our website and browsing it, certain information would be gathered and stored automatically , the web browser enables the below information to provide us, this would however not identify you personally. The below information helps us to make the site more user friendly and know the technology used to access the site:

  * Numeric IP Address 
  * The type of browser by which you are browsing the website
  * The time and date at which you might have accessed the website
  * The pictures and documents you download from the site and the pages you visit.

**‘Cookies’**

The Site employs cookies to speed your navigation of the Site, recognize you and your access privileges, and track your Site usage.

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored as text files by your Internet browser on your computer’s hard drive. Most Internet browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to refuse cookies from web sites or to remove cookies from your hard drive, but if you do, you will not be able to access or use portions of the Site. We need to use cookies to enable you to select products, place them in online shopping cart, and to finally purchase those products. We do keep a record of your browsing activity and purchase. Our cookies are not “spyware.”

When you make a transaction on Yuvastyle.com, the below information is gathered and will be used to make your order process smooth and all the further communication regarding the same:

  * Personal information which you enter to register on our website and order transaction i.e. Name, email id, gender, contact no. etc., these details might also be sent to a third party who work on our behalf for billing and shipping your order. We are also required by law to do the same. 
  * Your Yuvastyle Account related information such as your username, password account history, billing information and communication, transaction information and payment history, amount paid and other shipment/dispatch information.
  * Financial details related to your bank account or credit card/debit card or other payment mode and any other information which you agree to provide while processing your order.
  * Data collected during your interaction with Yuvastyle by Chats, messages or any other medium.

We use the above information for our internal analytics and also to simplify our marketing activities. 

Your account information is password-protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas, our Site uses industry-standard secure socket layer (SSL) encryption for financial transactions.

In case you wish to change, edit your current details, you can mail us at [support@yuvastyle.com](mailto:support@yuvastyle.com) or call us at 079-65445102.

Please note we might change some part of our privacy policy from time to time, you can review the same and also if you have any queries or need to address any grievances you can inform us and accordingly we can look into the same.
